Sister!
أخت!
Please
لو سمحت
(Lu Zhen'er, nursing graduate) bless me
(لو زينير، خريج التمريض) باركوني
for passing tomorrow's exam
تمنياتي لك بالتوفيق في امتحان الغد
and becoming a qualified nurse.
وأن تصبح ممرضة مؤهلة.
(Best fortune)
(أفضل حظ)
The best fortune!
حظاً سعيداً!
Someone is drowning!
أحدهم يغرق!
Who is it? Hurry!
من هذا؟ أسرعوا!
- Save him!
أنقذوه!
Someone is drowning!
أحدهم يغرق!
- Who can?
- أنقذوه! - من يستطيع؟
Move aside!
ابتعدوا جانباً!
I'm a nursing student! I know CPR!
أنا طالبة تمريض! أعرف الإسعافات الأولية والإنعاش القلبي الرئوي!
Save him.
أنقذه.
(Oh my, where am I?)
(يا إلهي، أين أنا؟)
(Why in ancient costumes?)
(لماذا يرتدون أزياءً قديمة؟)
(Am I dreaming?)
(هل أنا أحلم؟)
No!
لا!
- (This must be a nightmare.) - Now is the Shen hour.
- (لا بد أن هذا كابوس.) - الآن حان وقت شين.
By the late emperor's decree,
بموجب مرسوم الإمبراطور الراحل،
all consorts should
ينبغي على جميع الأزواج
(Xiao Wenjing, the new emperor) serve him on the road to the underworld.
(شياو وينجينغ، الإمبراطور الجديد) يخدمه في الطريق إلى العالم السفلي.
- The auspicious hour has come. - (This isn't right.)
- لقد حانت الساعة الميمونة. - (هذا ليس صحيحاً.)
(Isn't he Emperor Xiao Wenjing from Harem Turmoil?)
(أليس هو الإمبراطور شياو وينجينغ من مسلسل "اضطراب الحريم"؟)
(Why is he coming to me?)
(لماذا يأتي إليّ؟)
So this isn't a dream.
إذن هذا ليس حلماً.
I was just
كنت فقط
saving someone at the beach.
إنقاذ شخص ما على الشاطئ.
How am I here now?
كيف وصلت إلى هنا الآن؟
Consort Lu!
كونسورت لو!
Save me!
أنقذني!
I don't want to die!
لا أريد أن أموت!
Sister?
أخت؟
(Yindan, palace maid) Consort Lu!
(ييندان، خادمة القصر) القرينة لو!
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
(Sister,)
(أخت،)
(I thought you were dead.)
(ظننت أنك مت.)
(Am I dead too?)
(هل أنا ميت أيضاً؟)
So what people say online about seeing
إذن، ما يقوله الناس على الإنترنت عن رؤية
one's loved ones after death is true.
إن وجود أحباء المرء بعد الموت أمر صحيح.
Sister,
أخت،
I've missed you so much!
لقد اشتقت إليك كثيراً!
Consort Lu, what are you talking about?
يا قرينة لو، ما الذي تتحدثين عنه؟
How could I be your sister?
كيف يمكن أن أكون أختك؟
What
ماذا
did you just call me?
هل اتصلت بي للتو؟
Consort Lu.
كونسورت لو.
(This is insane.)
(هذا جنون.)
(In the prime of my youth,)
(في ريعان شبابي،)
(I actually transmigrated into Lu Zhen'er,)
(في الواقع، انتقلت إلى لو تشن إر)
(a bewitching consort)
(قرينة ساحرة)
(who is to be buried alive)
(الذي سيدفن حياً)
(with the late emperor.)
(مع الإمبراطور الراحل.)
(What a disastrous start!)
(يا لها من بداية كارثية!)
(Lu Zhen'er, the late emperor's consort) Oh,
(لو تشن إر، قرينة الإمبراطور الراحل) أوه،
my
لي
God!
إله!
You want to escape?
هل تريد الهروب؟
(I mustn't die!)
(يجب ألا أموت!)
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
I can divine fortunes!
أستطيع التنبؤ بالمستقبل!
I have clairvoyance!
لديّ قدرة على الاستبصار!
I'll help handle Her Majesty who rules behind the curtain
سأساعد في التعامل مع جلالتها التي تحكم من وراء الستار
and help you reclaim power!
ونساعدك على استعادة قوتك!
How dare you
كيف تجرؤ؟
sow discord between my mother and I!
أزرع الفتنة بيني وبين أمي!
Unforgivable!
لا يُغتفر!
Kill her!
اقتلها!
I am sorry!
أنا آسف!
Sorry!
آسف!
It wasn't intentional!
لم يكن ذلك مقصوداً!
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I
أنا
am
أكون
sorry!
آسف!
It's okay!
لا بأس!
♪When thunder roars♪
♪عندما يزمجر الرعد♪
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
Nice to meet you!
سعيد بلقائك!
Nice to meet you, too!
سُعدت برؤيتك!
(Fellow travelers.)
(أيها المسافرون الأعزاء.)
(When fellow travelers meet,)
(عندما يلتقي المسافرون)
(tears fill their eyes.)
(تمتلئ عيونهم بالدموع.)
Take her back to the harem.
أعدها إلى الحريم.
And clean this up.
ونظف هذا المكان.
(Is my life)
(هي حياتي)
(going to be restarted like this?)
(هل ستتم إعادة تشغيلها على هذا النحو؟)
(Sister,)
(أخت،)
(let's go.)
(دعنا نذهب.)
=His Chosen Favor=
=مفضلته المختارة=
(Nice to Meet You)
(سعيد بلقائك)
=Episode 1=
=الحلقة 1=
All gold!
ذهب خالص!
A glowing peacock!
طاووس متوهج!
Solid gold toad!
ضفدع من الذهب الخالص!
It's solid!
إنه متين!
No wonder the fortune-teller said
لا عجب أن قالت العرافة
my luck peaks in middle age.
يبلغ حظي ذروته في منتصف العمر.
The older I get, the better my fortune!
كلما تقدمت في السن، كلما تحسنت حظوظي!
I never thought I'd live
لم أتخيل يوماً أنني سأعيش
this lavish life
هذه الحياة المترفة
Gold's price is 980 now.
سعر الذهب الآن هو 980.
At this weight,
بهذا الوزن،
I'm being rich!
أنا أعيش حياة ثرية!
Pearl bracelets!
أساور من اللؤلؤ!
Jade bracelets!
أساور من اليشم!
What is this?
ما هذا؟
David.
ديفيد.
Never thought you're an artist.
لم أظن يوماً أنك فنان.
And a wealthy one.
وثريّ.
This is Golden Phoebe Nanmu wood, right?
هذا خشب نانمو الخاص بزهرة الفوبيا الذهبية، أليس كذلك؟
How much would this cost?
كم ستكون التكلفة؟
So great!
رائع جداً!
This is no different from sitting on a gold mountain.
هذا لا يختلف عن الجلوس على جبل من الذهب.
Stop staring. Let's talk.
توقف عن التحديق. هيا نتحدث.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
When did you travel through?
متى مررت بهذه المنطقة؟
Just now.
الآن.
So
لذا
that person in bed wasn't you, right?
الشخص الذي كان في السرير لم يكن أنت، أليس كذلك؟
Your Majesty, I adore you.
جلالتك، أنا أعشقك.
My heart yearns for you.
قلبي يتوق إليك.
So I came naturally.
لذا فقد أتيت بشكل طبيعي.
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
I have principles.
لدي مبادئ.
I was in a pit as soon as I traveled through.
لقد وقعت في حفرة بمجرد أن مررت بها.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
When did you travel through?
متى مررت بهذه المنطقة؟
Two years ago.
قبل عامين.
No wonder you seem
لا عجب أنك تبدو
nothing like a modern person.
لا يشبه الشخص العصري على الإطلاق.
Have you read that comic?
هل قرأت تلك القصة المصورة؟
I don't read comics.
أنا لا أقرأ القصص المصورة.
Then let me tell you
دعني أخبرك
about this comic's story.
حول قصة هذا الكتاب الهزلي.
The heroine is your mother, Empress Dowager Chen.
البطلة هي والدتك، الإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين.
The hero is your father.
البطل هو والدك.
Your mother loved your father,
كانت والدتك تحب والدك،
but he didn't love her.
لكنه لم يكن يحبها.
Using her family's influence, she forced him to marry her.
استغلت نفوذ عائلتها وأجبرته على الزواج منها.
For decades, he unwillingly endured physical and emotional torment.
على مدى عقود، تحمل رغماً عنه العذاب الجسدي والنفسي.
But tragic heroines never die easily.
لكن البطلات المأساويات لا يمتن بسهولة.
Later, your father died,
وفي وقت لاحق، توفي والدك.
yet your mother survived.
لكن والدتك نجت.
Where we are now is the comic's ending.
ما وصلنا إليه الآن هو نهاية القصة المصورة.
Not long after,
وبعد فترة وجيزة،
you'll die suddenly.
ستموت فجأة.
Empress Dowager Chen
الإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين
will be promoted, amass wealth and outlive her husband,
ستترقى، وتجمع ثروة طائلة ، وتعيش أطول من زوجها.
then her son.
ثم ابنها.
Just the cliche drama
مجرد دراما مبتذلة
of "I love you, but you don't".
من "أنا أحبك، لكنك لا تحبني".
That makes it entertaining!
هذا ما يجعله مسلياً!
We may show goodwill to Her Majesty.
قد نظهر حسن النية لجلالتها.
Opposing the heroine
معارضة البطلة
never ends well.
لا تنتهي الأمور على خير أبداً.
You are my father's consort,
أنتِ زوجة والدي،
who Her Majesty hates most.
الشخص الذي تكرهه جلالتها أكثر من غيره.
You think she'd accept your goodwill?
أتظن أنها ستتقبل حسن نيتك؟
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
I'm her biggest thorn in the side.
أنا أكبر شوكة في خاصرتها.
Since we can't befriend her,
بما أننا لا نستطيع مصادقتها،
there's only one other option.
ليس هناك سوى خيار واحد آخر.
What?
ماذا؟
Strike first.
ابدأ بالهجوم.
Let's take her down.
هيا بنا نهزمها.
Her Majesty is here.
جلالتها هنا.
(Chen Wanyi, Empress Dowager) Mother, what has angered you?
(تشين وان يي، الإمبراطورة الأرملة) أمي، ما الذي أغضبك؟
Tell me, so I can enjoy it too.
أخبرني بذلك حتى أستمتع به أنا أيضاً.
Where is Lu Zhen'er?
أين لو زينير؟
Lu Zhen'er?
لو زينير؟
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
The burial consort you rescued!
رفيقة الدفن التي أنقذتها!
Don't play dumb with me!
لا تتظاهر بالغباء معي!
No burial consorts here,
لا يوجد مرافقون للدفن هنا،
but the newly appointed Consort Lu.
لكن القرينة لو المعينة حديثاً.
She is my consort,
هي قرينتي،
unrelated to Father.
لا علاقة له بالأب.
You can appoint anyone as consort,
يمكنك تعيين أي شخص كقرين،
except Lu Zhen'er.
باستثناء لو زينير.
You want to select consorts for me.
تريد أن تختار لي قرينات.
So I chose Lu Zhen'er.
لذلك اخترت لو Zhen'er.
Why aren't you pleased?
لماذا أنت غير راضٍ؟
She is your father's consort.
إنها زوجة والدك.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
Are you jealous of her
هل تشعر بالغيرة منها؟
as she had Father's exclusive favor
لأنها كانت تحظى بتفضيل والدها الحصري
and now mine?
والآن دوري؟
Xiao Wenjing!
شياو ون جينغ!
Mother,
الأم،
Lu Zhen'er is my woman.
لو Zhen'er هي امرأتي.
If you want to take her,
إذا كنت تريد اصطحابها،
fine.
بخير.
Eunuch Fu!
الخصي فو!
(Fu An, Head Eunuch) Draft an edict now
(فو آن، رئيس الخصيان) صِغ مرسومًا الآن
by stating that the new emperor has passed away.
بإعلان وفاة الإمبراطور الجديد.
The throne is passed to Her Majesty.
ينتقل العرش إلى جلالتها.
Once you become the empress,
بمجرد أن تصبحي الإمبراطورة،
you can take Lu Zhen'er away.
يمكنك أن تأخذ Lu Zhen'er بعيدًا.
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
Xiao Wenjing,
شياو ون جينغ
do you truly think I won't kill you?
هل تعتقد حقاً أنني لن أقتلك؟
Go ahead!
تفضل!
I've waited so long for this day.
لقد انتظرت هذا اليوم طويلاً.
Sooner or later,
عاجلا أو آجلا،
you'll pay the price for coveting
ستدفع ثمن الطمع
your father's things.
أغراض والدك.
Is your face alright?
هل وجهك بخير؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
What did you do for work before?
ماذا كنت تعمل سابقاً؟
You have great explosive power!
لديك قوة تفجيرية هائلة!
An actor?
ممثل؟
I didn't work.
لم أعمل.
Where is your cool linen pants?
أين بنطالك الكتاني الأنيق؟
It's too hot here.
الجو حار جداً هنا.
Without air conditioning,
بدون تكييف هواء،
I cut mine shorter.
قصصت شعري أقصر.
Then what did you do?
ثم ماذا فعلت؟
Nothing much.
لا شيء يُذكر.
Just scheming against my dad's
مجرد تدبير مكائد ضد والدي
illegitimate children
الأطفال غير الشرعيين
for the family fortune.
من أجل ثروة العائلة.
You just said
لقد قلت للتو
you want to take Her Majesty down.
تريدون إسقاط جلالتها.
Any viable plans?
هل هناك أي خطط قابلة للتطبيق؟
It's 2025 now!
نحن الآن في عام 2025!
The legendary Nine Purple Li Fire Luck has begun.
لقد بدأ موسم الحظ الأسطوري لـ" نيبر لي فاير لاك" ذو اللون الأرجواني التاسع.
An era for heroines to dominate.
عصرٌ تهيمن فيه البطلات.
If we team up...
إذا تعاونا...
We can crush all obstacles.
بإمكاننا تحطيم جميع العقبات.
Lu Zhen'er,
لو زينير،
aren't you going home?
ألن تذهب إلى المنزل؟
I've got everything here
كل شيء موجود هنا
and my sister.
وأختي.
Why would I go back?
لماذا سأعود؟
Your sister?
أختك؟
Travel through time with you?
هل ستسافر عبر الزمن معي؟
No.
لا.
She just looks exactly like my sister.
إنها تشبه أختي تماماً.
Why won't you go back to find your real sister,
لماذا لا تعود للبحث عن أختك الحقيقية؟
instead of calling this imposter?
بدلاً من وصف هذا الشخص بالمحتال؟
Because
لأن
she died.
ماتت.
I can't find her in the modern era.
لا أستطيع العثور عليها في العصر الحديث.
Maybe
ربما
Heaven sent me here
لقد أرسلني الله إلى هنا
to reunite with her.
لكي يلتقي بها مجدداً.
I'll assign Yindan to you
سأكلفك بمهمة يندان
as your personal maid.
كخادمة شخصية لك.
(I never dreamed of wearing such a gorgeous robe.)
(لم أحلم قط بارتداء رداء بهذه الروعة.)
(So beautiful!)
(جميل جداً!)
(So many girls yearn to become)
(كثير من الفتيات يتوقن لأن يصبحن مثلهن)
(the empress or noble consort.)
(الإمبراطورة أو القرينة النبيلة.)
(It seems I'm almost there!)
(يبدو أنني على وشك الوصول!)
(I'm about to reach the peak of my life!)
(أنا على وشك بلوغ ذروة حياتي!)
Truly a bewitching consort!
يا لها من قرينة ساحرة!
A femme fatale!
امرأة فاتنة!
Indeed!
بالفعل!
Washing feet in the imperial court?
غسل الأقدام في البلاط الإمبراطوري؟
Is that even allowed?
هل هذا مسموح به أصلاً؟
Why wouldn't it be?
ولماذا لا يكون كذلك؟
Here, what I say goes.
هنا، كلمتي هي المسموعة.
Alright then!
حسناً إذاً!
- Soaking feet in the Throne Room! - Awesome!
- نقع القدمين في قاعة العرش! - رائع!
Utterly disgraceful!
أمرٌ مخزٍ للغاية!
- A femme fatale! - Did my phone come with me?
- امرأة فاتنة! - هل هاتفي معي؟
I want to take a photo and post it on Moments.
أريد التقاط صورة ونشرها على تطبيق Moments.
Posting on Moments now?
هل تنشر الآن على تطبيق Moments؟
Comfortable!
مريح!
I'm the Foot Soak King!
أنا ملك نقع القدمين!
Soon this entire city
قريباً ستشمل هذه المدينة بأكملها
could be yours.
قد يكون ملكك.
That would be amazing!
سيكون ذلك رائعاً!
Tomorrow, I'll help you deal with the harem.
غداً، سأساعدك في التعامل مع الحريم.
(Noble Consort Qing, the new emperor's consort)
(الزوجة النبيلة تشينغ، زوجة الإمبراطور الجديد)
Consort Xi is here.
الملكة شي هنا.
I'm late.
أنا متأخر.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
You're always late,
أنت دائماً متأخر،
keeping everyone waiting.
إبقاء الجميع في الانتظار.
(Beauty Yu, the new emperor's consort) You think as Her Majesty's niece,
(الجميلة يو، قرينة الإمبراطور الجديد) أنت تفكر كابنة أخت جلالتها،
you can break the palace rules?
هل يمكنك مخالفة قواعد القصر؟
Rules?
قواعد؟
You...
أنت...
A mere Beauty
جمالٌ لا يُضاهى
dares to lecture me on rules?
هل يجرؤ على إلقاء محاضرة عليّ بشأن القواعد؟
I heard His Majesty
سمعت جلالته
brought back Consort Lu from the sacrificial pit yesterday.
أعادوا القرينة لو من حفرة التضحية أمس.
Step forward and let me see
تقدم للأمام ودعني أرى
if you're a peerless beauty.
إذا كنتِ تتمتعين بجمال لا مثيل له.
Greetings, all the beautiful sisters.
تحية طيبة لجميع الأخوات الجميلات.
Don't you dare dodge!
إياك أن تتهرب!
Instinctive reaction.
رد فعل غريزي.
Guards!
حراس!
Consort Lu
كونسورت لو
has publicly affronted me.
لقد أهانني علنًا.
Slap her.
صفعها.
I didn't dodge intentionally,
لم أتفادى الأمر عن قصد،
but I
لكنني
was momentarily dazzled by your beauty.
لقد انبهرت بجمالك للحظات.
I've long heard of your celestial grace and beauty.
لطالما سمعت عن جمالك وروعتك السماوية.
Seeing you today, I find you live up to your reputation.
برؤيتك اليوم، أجد أنك ترقى إلى مستوى سمعتك.
I beg
أتوسل
for Your Highness's forgiveness.
أرجو من سموكم العفو.
What a silver tongue you have.
يا لك من متحدث فصيح!
No wonder both the late emperor and His Majesty favor you.
لا عجب أن يحظى كل من الإمبراطور الراحل وجلالة الملك بتقديرك.
Consort Xi,
القرينة شي،
enough.
كافٍ.
We're sisters here.
نحن أخوات هنا.
Don't make such an ugly scene.
لا تُحدث مثل هذا المشهد البشع.
This bewitching consort isn't my sister.
هذه الزوجة الساحرة ليست أختي.
By your looks,
من مظهرك،
you're nothing special.
أنت لست مميزاً.
Why did both emperors treat you so exceptionally?
لماذا عاملك كلا الإمبراطورين بهذه المعاملة الاستثنائية؟
So
لذا
are you exceptionally
هل أنت استثنائي؟
gifted in bed?
هل هو موهوب في الفراش؟
Consort Xi,
القرينة شي،
- you... - Since when do you dictate to me?
- أنت... - منذ متى وأنت تملي عليّ؟
Emperors' mind is unfathomable.
عقل الأباطرة لا يُدرك.
I don't know
لا أعرف
why they favored me alone.
لماذا فضلوني أنا وحدي؟
Consort Xi,
القرينة شي،
if you're so curious,
إذا كنت فضولياً للغاية،
go ask them yourself.
اذهب واسألهم بنفسك.
You wretch!
يا لك من بائس!
Guards!
حراس!
Seize her!
أمسك بها!
I'll tear up her mouth!
سأمزق فمها!
- Yes!
- نعم!
Let go of me!
اتركني!
Truly a seductress!
فاتنة بكل معنى الكلمة!
Parading around in such shameless clothing!
التباهي بهذه الملابس الفاضحة!
She is dressed like this
إنها ترتدي ملابس كهذه
to please men.
لإرضاء الرجال.
Zisu! Yanyu!
يا إلهي! يانيو!
Strip her!
انزعي عنها ملابسها!
Drag her out of the Yonghe Palace to let the people there witness
أخرجوها من قصر يونغهي ليشهد الناس هناك
how shameless she is.
يا لها من وقحة!
- Yes!
- نعم!
Let go of me!
اتركني!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'll do it myself!
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي!
What's happening at the Yonghe Palace?
ما الذي يحدث في قصر يونغهي؟
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
word came from the Yonghe Palace.
وردت أنباء من قصر يونغهي.
Consort Lu was stripped by Consort Xi.
جُرِّدت المحظية لو من ملابسها على يد المحظية شي.
Will Your Majesty go see?
هل سيذهب جلالتكم لرؤية ذلك؟
After today's ordeal,
بعد محنة اليوم،
Consort Lu will likely become a laughingstock.
من المرجح أن تصبح كونسورت لو مادة للسخرية.
That means nothing.
هذا لا يعني شيئاً.
I want her dead.
أريدها ميتة.
(Lu Zhen'er)
(لو زينير)
♪Moonlight beyond the pass sighs for restless fluttering petals♪
♪ضوء القمر وراء الممر يتنهد لبتلات الزهور المتراقصة المضطربة♪
♪Life is fleeting, spring rivers turn cold♪
الحياة زائلة، وأنهار الربيع تبرد.
♪Clear boat, misty waters frost again, shore willows hasten yellow♪
♪قارب صافٍ، مياه ضبابية تتجمد من جديد، وأشجار الصفصاف على الشاطئ تُسرع في اصفرارها♪
♪Sitting alone by the window, watching the mournful sunset♪
♪أجلس وحيداً بجوار النافذة، أشاهد غروب الشمس الحزين♪
♪In the courtyard's music room, wind recounts the past♪
♪في غرفة الموسيقى بالفناء، تروي الرياح الماضي♪
♪Empty lanes still sing of childhood days♪
♪لا تزال الأزقة الخالية تغني بذكريات أيام الطفولة♪
♪On stage, I mimic your songs, entrusting thoughts to recklessness♪
على المسرح، أقلد أغنياتك، وأترك ​​أفكاري للجرأة.
♪Where is my love today♪
أين حبي اليوم؟
♪I ponder whom to gaze upon, a thousand green hills frosted white♪
أتأمل فيمن أنظر إليه، ألف تلة خضراء مغطاة بالصقيع الأبيض
♪Awaiting crabapple blossoms, a fleeting dream♪
♪أنتظر أزهار التفاح البري، حلم عابر♪
♪I ponder whom to share a toast with, let life laugh at my folly♪
أتأمل مع من أرفع نخبًا، دع الحياة تضحك على حماقتي.
♪Those lost within the play are the most insane♪
♪أولئك التائهون في المسرحية هم الأكثر جنوناً♪
♪In the courtyard's music room, wind recounts the past♪
♪في غرفة الموسيقى بالفناء، تروي الرياح الماضي♪
♪Empty lanes still sing of childhood days♪
♪لا تزال الأزقة الخالية تغني بذكريات أيام الطفولة♪
♪On stage, I mimic your songs, entrusting thoughts to recklessness♪
على المسرح، أقلد أغنياتك، وأترك ​​أفكاري للجرأة.
♪Where is my love today♪
أين حبي اليوم؟
♪I ponder whom to share a toast with, let life laugh at my folly♪
أتأمل مع من أرفع نخبًا، دع الحياة تضحك على حماقتي.
♪Those lost within the play are the most insane♪
♪أولئك التائهون في المسرحية هم الأكثر جنوناً♪
♪Only then knowing this life's yearning is the deepest folly♪
♪عندها فقط يصبح إدراك شوق هذه الحياة هو الحماقة الأعمق♪